Here's to
you dear.
It is. It it was.
To Iraq it
is.
There are. Exactly. Five minutes.
First of all let me explain and I
find myself. Very reasonably and
not at all surprised it started
back in World War two during
a wood game of campaign I was
a captain in the Marine
Corps. Captain needs
a top sergeant but I really had
the best name was Joe only.
The Ted was running into a
living hell I guess I got
a little care of. Saving
my life was he. Carried
a bullet so close to his lung surgery was
impossible during the time the medics
that cept we became great friends
after the war I watched him build
a home I watched him become
successful we were closer than
most brothers one afternoon
six months ago I sent for Joe
I knew I was going to break his heart and
all I could think about was whether it
wouldn't have been better for both this.
If he had allowed me to die on that beach
that. You know Greg you're
the only guy in town
this time of day is coming
over to see anyway oh. There's
a new housing development gone up over
Piedmont what you think about buying
a corner lot taking up a new
market might be an idea
a lot of you. Look like you had
a problem it's too heavy to carry it almost
is too. We've been through it can't be
too serious maybe talk about. Going to
mean throwing fifteen years of friendship
right out the window. Real
friendship won't bend easy.
Are you happy being married tomorrow and
Joe Don't tell me it's none of my the.
Word that means a lot of things that state
of being I never asked myself I got
a beautiful wife lovely home good business
I can expect and I think it's been great
it's going to be unhappy not really
Joe Perhaps you haven't realized how
little time you've been spending at home
how many evenings you've given to the bed
Myra is
a fine woman. When she married you she was
in love but no one wants to be alone all
the time now she'd like to do
something about it. Say she
told you the talk and they. Ask you to
represent are two it was more my idea than
I don't. Don't know how to say it
without making.
People mate with no thought of being
anything but friend circumstances throw them
together then they discover in each other
many mutual interests they begin to
anticipate their next meeting
and then the next until finally
one day they. Both realize they're
very much in love OK don't dress it
up who's the guy. I'm in love with
a girl I want to marry. Then the way it is
and it's the most difficult thing I've ever
had to say to anyone are you sure Craig
are you sure you know what you're
doing and I'm in love with you.
But he wanted. I'd like
Myra to go away get
a divorce you know voice had
a lot of respect and admiration for
the Bible and they like this take
a lot of God Like I said
a real friendship doesn't bend easy. When
there's. A kind of like a one. In
a couple of days kicking around.
When. Why.
Why. Why
why. Yes. Please
cancel the rest of my appointment. When.
The time. And the rest of my life.
Was OK.
And I can tell.
You today I told him.
What did. That surround. It getting
just give him
a couple of days to think. Help
and.
Do you believe that when we
first. Tried to pull them. Up we
respected. We tried to
comply with everything we.
Did make today. I never wanted to I
didn't think I could possibly phone
anyone. Having I'm not ashamed of
you I'm not afraid of the
truth I don't believe we have
things wrong. Crazy.
Just got my best as well I think there was
a real pretty. And you were there the
night she would warn I kind of. I gave
away many thanks to do. I
never saw two people better so to reach the
top Even moment. Sometimes in the best
think that way on. What's wrong.
Thank you thank you something
you can't prove
a thing just the other day when I was in
it with the people about the branch still
Garley even listen to me look like
a rug miles away ever since then you've
been buzzing around like like something was
bothering that. You know little
girl on the right thing isn't the easiest
thing in the world. You've got to look
deep inside the real. Wealth of the
past few days that's just what
I've been doing looking down deep inside
of. Them for the right answer and I
finally found. Sounds like
an important decision.
And
a tough one to probably change my whole
life Myra's to some wrongdoing on my. I
don't think anything could be worse job of
a very very couple has their ups and downs
even Mama knew you had some bad moments
but honestly if you just have patience
and everything you say words. Sometimes.
Sometimes. To me if there was a male it's
a way home. For
my to you're home going to be home early
I'm thinking about something I want to
talk to you about OK then about fifteen
or twenty minutes. Just remember Joe
everything here is the words. Live in
a dream world when.
You're.
Not in the right state over Sure chocking
off the place good ones already.
But it looks like with them. To the
lady we've got a breeze if it's
a charter as that itself that's come everybody
always shoots somebody else and so.
I was we. I think we got everything pretty
well straight. Which mind going over
that first part for me just as well. I was
sitting in bed reading when Joe came in
he was wet in the period. I
couldn't imagine what was wrong
he just walked over and pulled me out of
bed to be with trunk. Crazy or something
firmly against the dresser that he was
going to kill me he started for me
again when I opened the
drawer took out the gun shot
he just. Looked at it
and he said oh it was.
Going to be all right
you just rest there for
a minute. You know this place is all you
know like you and I just before you.
Now we have
a voice going directly to the. Right. I
want the section of the room covered from A
to Z.
Several shots about night stand in this
vessel here getting close you know the kind
of stuff I won't cover the
place like they're planning on
a big day in court the guy that makes them
think that. Having the doubt of the self
. The holder of suspicion about that is
up to you legal eagles the picture of.
Always done if you want to talk to your
client have at it because I think you're
down town about two minutes.
I don't understand. I don't understand
you don't know tension understand
me all these questions those men and
they're taking pictures think of pain
I'm afraid. Just pretty much.
Nothing to be alarmed about. Tennis
Patty question Tappan things which
they don't need to. Tell me the truth
Lieutenant brand they plan to hold you on
suspicion of. I am I going to do
how can I make them believe there
will be my job done. I tried to
kill why couldn't the end just
a. Matter. I
love Joe as much as anyone
could. But I knew it
to do the actions when caused by said and
then he had several days to think about
what he was going to do and he been
successful it would have been premeditated
murder. I'm afraid I
don't I know it's going
to be difficult. Just.
I still mean that own life
wasn't that just when.
They had
a brain injury mine district attorney
asked for my early life is approved she
killed Julie's in cold
blood I think we got
a new twist this time if we go to calls
it claims it was an attack of violence
carefully today the next security I tell
you No Wonder Woman has impressed me any
more yet I'm going to be
a beaut this gal good coming in Brunswick
bug anybody besides carless I think that
leaves woman wouldn't have
a prayer course back in session I'll call
rewriting type of the retardation to that
one.
Just the guy down quarterback and said.
Nah I don't have to be in there you can't
take pictures in the court room you
were the first officer to report
a scene of the murder Yes sir my partner
and I were cruising that area when we got
the call refusal that you're exactly what
you found well this is leaving Mr Carlson
were there when we arrived Mr Carlson said
Mrs Levy called him and soon as he got
there the whole the police with the signs
of struggle. Mrs Lees wasn't marked or
rude in anyone not that I could tell you
to see anything about her clothing or
person or anything at all that
indicated that there had been
a struggle now so I think that's all. And
no question Sergeant Hill
you are connected with
a crime that's right and if you know that
it was raining the night of the murder
does or would you please tell the court
how that affected your findings now I had
a picture please. OK.
This dark spot was one of the first things
we checked out that water and probably
came from Jodi's clothing from the way we
can piece it together if the right there
did make
a move from the shot. In other words
reduction is that there could not have been
a struggle. I object to this question
calls for the conclusion of the witness
stand did you find any
water spots anyplace
else in the nose that you could.
Downhill What makes you so certain Gilead
did not move closer to Mrs Lee then the
area was. The weather will run
through the why would require quite
a concentration was that means the
back then would have to stand
a spell but this is leaves and he came
right over to her and to the question
started prosecuting Tony's well
able to argue with Kate. One
about some of the other people and that.
They could have good water and that could
they not wait check that out the rain had
stopped by the time the first police unit
arrived but it hadn't stopped when Ira could
and I was that in one spot long enough
to dampen that but. They sure could
have thank you that. And then
she stated that the doctor again the
pressure was there until the brought out the
gun. Leaves and the gun was in the dresser
drawer Yes Did you point out where Mr
Lee's was at the time she shot him she said
he was rushing farther from where they
started the bed this is
a gray where by the on the left by Mrs
Levy why did your investigation bear the
conclusion. Please explain why on the
best you know Oprah filming the light
and how he knocked her against the stairwell
Surely some of these bottles would
have been overturned. Then abruptly
this one of the photographs he ordered
taken. Don't you see anything at all the
stir on her about that. Those are now.
Gone and well according to Mrs Bailey
the spot where Mr Levy standing at the
time she shot him was about ten feet from
where he felt was not possible no sex
according to the coroner's report the
bacon was shot through the heart and died
instantly the words to mean what about the
wall ten feet after he was dead that's
about it witnessed.
Senate Bradley how many years you've
been on the Glee. Twenty two and
during that time when
you say you witnessed
a number of people suffering from
hysteria I'faith. And what would you say
were the first signed
Terry or. Incoherency
unable to make
a decision sort of the last and common
sense and when you say it was likely for
a woman who just killed
a man to be self brings
a mystery. Yet. And would
not be within the realm of
possibility for this woman to
mistake her let some right come to
a snap judgment direction that would be
entirely incorrect. Possibility then
wouldn't it be possible
for a woman in such
a state of hysteria to think she was thrown
against the dresser when in reality she
was thrown against a
nearby wall she could be
a bozo. You
know you had
a pretty social Day three visited one was
from the newspaper today and came over to
tell me not to way cause hope he's an artist
and wondered if there was anything he
could do Craig going badly funny there's
nothing new to worry about so don't try to
find. Everything Oh
darling I know it's been
a difficult two weeks for you but tomorrow
should see the end of the testimony how
does it know whether someplace like
a field marshal doesn't mind losing battle
for long as he wins the war you'll save
his big emanation later last week. At
several top of the very anxious to
help you I'm sure as evidence will add
a lot of weight and I think I'm going to
let you testified to. I remember once
you're on the stand Willis will try to
cut to read I'm not afraid of something
judge of that you're on the fate of these
things going wrong I can achieve that
attacks.
No I says does is some wrong thing Elmira
said I don't see why and I think they
were. And you ever seen Jolie
before when he was quite angry.
A couple times in matter of fact he was
quite upset the first time I resigned
somebody accused him of giving
a dishonest com Try to get him in trouble
with bullies Joe hurt him pretty bad then
Jolie did have
a bad temper when he would upset.
Them but that was not often because
there in the night of
Gilead dead Did he seem
normal to you. Upset smiling that
was upset and said he'd been doing
a lot of thinking of the bridge to big
decision if he'd tell you what that decision
was. No separate but he decided with
changes whole lives and Myra's to
that will be all thank you there and become
of that phone conversation Jolie had
with his wife tell us exactly
what you overheard. That was
a long time ago just tell us those things
you can remember well I remember him
saying for her to stay home and then doing
a lot of thanking want to talk about over
there and I guess that's about all that
happened you know it was Julie definitely
had something to talk out with his wife
but that's the way it sounded Now mistakes
are in the defense counsel is open
much about Jolie's temper you say you
were present when Jolie beat up on the
cute. Would you say the deletes was quite
angry them on the list of ever saying
and the but that's all I had
come in to him is always live in
a dildo. No Joni's was more angry on that
occasion than you ever saw him why didn't
he kill the man did someone stop the fight
to know we were all glad the same guy
that anyway we knew all Joe had in
mind was a Russian mob. And sure did
a good job of Jillian's was more anger than
you had ever seen him you claim you had
no intention of killing now can you say
on the oath that you've taken that he was
angry enough to kill his wife
No my guess not thank you
because there is.
And if you recall any instance
the warrior has been displayed
a violent temper yet. There was
a time just before we were married Joe had
an argument with one of his employees
and the two men front jumping consulting
the other man had to spend the next two
months in the hospital and whether time
after marriage when your husband showed
a tendency toward violence several
whenever anything annoyed him.
If someone said something that
displeased him if you into
a temper we argued often because then
that night when he came home wet
blind with theory you had good
reason to think he would carry us
a good reason to think that believed was
a man of bile that is what you
believe is not mislead nor
do you think any other woman would have
reacted as you did I know they would no one
wants to kill them but no one
wants to be killed by you in it.
This is the it is that I wanted you and
your husband been married to us and we
married your husband what was your financial
condition. I don't understand why I'm
sorry I mean when you rich
moderately wealthy I had
a good job what I I was looking for
a job when I meant to be. And
when you say your husband was
a man of means I mean did he have some
property I'm sure and perhaps he had ten.
Judging by how much would you say your
husband was worth is that that is including
insurance I don't know the let
me tell you your husband Mrs
Leeds that's in the state of more than three
quarters of the million dollars That's
quite an inheritance for
you from unemployment to
a need seven hundred fifty thousand dollars
in two years when you say that was
a very lucrative two years work this is
the objection to the prosecution will
refrain from any more questions of this
nature that last statement will be stricken
from the record the jury is asked to
dissipate that leaves when you married your
husband were you in the cross were you
in love with your husband at the time is
that no the lesson two years
you no longer love to love is
a very strong emotion Mrs Leeds how could
you turn it off so quickly. I just
love him and he went into
a fatal one to tell him that's not true
then when did you tell your husband you
were no longer in love with him I
don't remember. Did you ask your
husband for
a divorce. And what was Mr
Lee's answer he just said he
wanted to think about it you know was late
when you suddenly told your husband you
want to divorce instead of becoming angry
he answered he wanted to think about it
now is that correct yes and if you ask this
court to believe that Mr Leeds returned
home and that they leaving
without so much as
a single word trying to kill you yes then
tell us what to leave how do you explain
the fact that when you first can we say
shocked your husband by asking him for the
boys he did nothing. I don't know I don't
know that will be omitted and.
Brierly would have us believe that when
her husband reached their apartment
immediately made an attempt to kill her
he had to kill in self-defense but what
concrete reasons have you been given that
Mrs Leeth felt she was forced to husband
only that he became furious when she told
him she no longer love but she wanted to
. Why did my release claim to want to
divorce in the first place just that they
were no longer than love and yet not one
single witness has been brought before
this court to indicate that any discord
existed between the leaves let me tell you
ladies and gentlemen during there was no
discord in the marriage of killed leads
only in that of his wife Myra and I'm
precious woman marriage in better position
with Jolie's death their position was
still improved the location of the body
the placement and trajectory of the bullet
that killed Leeds the lack of signs of
a struggle all of these facts
facts that against my early story
of self-defense could there be an honest
doubt in your minds as to the guilt of
this woman that there isn't just tell
them. My really has given no reason why
she would have wanted to divorce Julie's
except that she fell out of the Islam
such
a fickle thing that one can fall in love one
week not the next with no apparent reason
Myra leads have awakened one morning decided
to ask her husband of two years for
that was no but bitterly
with my relief that she was
a jobless when she met
your leads he saw in him
a stepping stone to an easy life when she
was ready to move on she realized that
Jody could only be
a monetary value to her that. So that when
he came home to discuss whatever it was
he was discussed he shot my
really shot them killed her
husband for
a handful of gold that is why the state
charges merrily. With Murder in the first
degree is counsel for the defense
ready to address the jury.
This has been
a long and grueling trial not only
for the defense the red this is well
you've heard the arguments and counter-arguments
fact encounter fact very uncommon
. For the past hour and fifteen minutes
you've heard the prosecution parade before
you every piece of circumstantial evidence
and you endo and playing conjecture that
he could muster conjecture that would both
or his claim that my really guilty of
murdering. All of this conjecture
at the end result has been that
the state claims my really killed Joe Levy
because their story about the moment of
violence he was faced with differed from
that of the bully and because she could
give no clear reason why she suddenly would
want to divorce her that if Myra lead
had a sound reason suddenly
desiring a divorce
a reason that would measurably add to our
happiness even the prosecution knows it
would have no case well my really did
have a reason for asking Joli for
a divorce my really in
love with another man why.
Now remember you were the jury are not
here to determine the right to my relief
emotion as
a woman only to determine if she shot her
husband in an act of premeditation it
is not for you to decide whether or not
my really did the right thing. And it
is for you to decide if in telling
a husband about the man she loved. To
arouse in him an anger so intense.
So now you as we. Bring him
forward to confirm this story
line you Jolie better than anyone that I
know the man his wife is in love with
and that.
Any further demonstration of this
character in this courtroom will declare.
My falling in love with my really
accident but my wanting to marry.
Was with strong intent as was generally
intent when he decided if he could no
longer have it why no other man would All
right ladies and gentlemen there isn't
a single one of you who wouldn't have
struggled my release for life with she acted
in self-defense. That story.
That to to bring out the truth
your verdict must be not.
Guilty the gallery carried the daily ten
but if that's the. Goal is whether the
mother when the jury on the science. Has
no doubt about it I got the biggest ascent
of murders I have since the
Chinese invented gunfire.
Bank. On the way back to.
Capri as ancient and intending as
Mediterranean with the rest. May not be
the world's greatest pro sounded good to
me. I thought we could be married next
week take
a boat to Rome they're right it happened.
Darling you know they're wonderful.
Wonderful but you know next week is almost.
Nil and. The sooner we get away the
better it will be. From now on you're not
going to have any reason to think of
anything about me.
About giving you I'm sorry I'm late but Mom
wasn't feeling well and last minute she
decided. To let me have to
come back and Myra that
everything turned out OK
Thank you. Both to be appy
again could I talk. It's about.
You know it's going to the
den. But I write to the city
of the.
It's about Joe in the last night he was
alive that night I thought it was my night
drop by to tell him about the wedding. Just
before I left he asked me to my letter
and I put it in my pocket I forgot all
about it until I put my taps on again and
it addressed to you.
Well like I promised
a lot of thinking I've been trying to
figure out best way for all of this is my
first met my big issues out of my league
she was interested in things that I didn't
understand like. But then like the boat
one night she told me she loved me and I.
Thought. In. Les. Rare
I got married right away for a
couple of months living with
a parent I didn't love or. Worship and.
One day we had an I my Raton and she
never love me goes without saying and I
walked in circles today
finally I asked if she wanted
a divorce and she said yes and.
Mindedness I got mad because I
realized that the only reason to never marry
me I told her that no man was going to
live on what it takes me most to me.
And going along the past few months
my was. Not
a new. Number some kind of an artist by.
Her out that she didn't know she was at
some plan going to see her tonight and it's
. No good Greg but I do love her
she decided not to stay with me
and when you know the truth
the woman My know that in the
in the way she's already destroyed me
and she doesn't end up destroying.
Did I cause trouble by
forgetting about the right.
Don't.
One could. Come to the Q.
From. My early shots and children.
That is why the stage on whose mind
the murdered perceivably cause no
one to convince.
Me to move yet my name.
Breaks out which meant
that to give the appearance
of life. I can this is that
a way of dominating all rules. That this
is that they're. Not like that went
on to that I'm afraid because
of my read. That way before
that you see this is
a pretty strange you know they
call it cloud and. That's because
a lot of men are just getting started of
around here. I have a lot of dreams about
a vital. I think it's our lives just two
doors down and it got lost and he was
right now to. Take some of the cases turned
out going to Charlie you didn't care
you got acquitted you could be living like
a mother right no way but the law. Got
a lot of other legal adults too but for
me my favorite evidence is that Margaret.
You know Myra long time we
were pregnant college I was
a music major and I was knee deep in art
every American. Plays like an angel
but my but Mary is an angel and
I guess he thought. He had.
Nothing earth shattering for anybody
except. The very much in love with her.
When with that. Beard that was
a. Strange engagement marriage
in between that was married one begins. You
know that you're here she married it on
you don't mind if I work on
it most of the sunlight.
A IRA and you need. To lead
people to
a different range are
often Mara money. Having
a prospect. We had
a scrap on that subject and she might lead
the rest right. Point about her knowing
the day I was when we met and.
Right at this juncture I'd like to make
a point of honor and I refuse the
marry again after that afternoon.
Where they. Didn't. Even
ask leave for the glorious
months of the crazy and
awful night with. No hope.
There's
a lot working against your idea that I still
may get like you want to do but what I
got working against is trial I
didn't to offer to help I did
but there this is America he didn't want
me to come to Syria no reason say I knew
or I couldn't quite figure that
out I guess it was because he was
a great ARE BEING A lot would sway the
jury against recent use. When he was very
approach free to make a lawyer
a lawyer just plain smart. I watched at
trial every single day and you never do
a miss where I would like
a crack at improving your impression on
the audience my pretenses right and I do
like. The really classical about the
French accent so it didn't carry when the
glass the fireplace. Go to that part
of the concern Well I'm going to
quietly I will see you again only
you know that last day of the trial
that you were the man of
merit life and thinks
a kind lady is an admirer
straight out. With
a lot of before she was
a beaut that was the best piece of dramatics
I've ever seen her and I really owe
you an awful lot going on
a limb like that by Mr
Holmes by McAlpin. Who
. Who.
I was expecting your body to be I'm.
Not quite sure I know how to make that.
I was expecting it but
I know. That's right.
No thanks I just want to
talk. About are engaged
let's not make it why not and why not
this very minute two people in love can't
wait Myra that's the way with people
and not in the same crank someone.
Might say you say you're hopelessly
irretrievably in love with. I want to hear
you say it Ira I'm all you have. Suddenly
remembered there was someone else I
had let go of someone like
Hope All right you know
I met him he seemed very
much. To men in love with.
The arrangement I read. What
happened when it was on the.
I don't think so fact I
don't think you ever made
a mistake before in your life I don't want
to tell you I just the truth the truth
is I have I'm going to marry and you were
in love with you were going to marry him
the day I met you I don't want to
stop and let someone talk about it
received this letter yes it. Was kind of
a trick. Down.
Like I promised I've been doing a lot
of thinking and trying to figure out
a way to see when I first met my right
because he was out of my league he was
interested in things I didn't understand
like our news Meriden were created not
with you. In love with some kind of an
artist I can't figure out what he's doing to
you but I know he must have some kind of.
Going to see her tonight and when you try
and keep He's no good but I do love Lucy
decide not to stay with me and wanted you
to share in the woman Myra's it easy this
is already destroyed me I just hope she
doesn't end up destroying you.
I don't believe children to
be able to recognize writing
articles. On the detail with
a miserable jealous man no matter the prove
something much different Joe offered
you
a divorce without any money you didn't
wanted that you knew there was only one way
to get you'll have to do more than thank
your have to prove I'm free. I CAN DO WHAT
I WANT got
a plan very carefully in mind get Joe's
money you had to kill him to guarantee your
freedom you made me fall in love I
wonder how I want to merge with white I
was trying to quit
a job in the bank pretty No one
can take me anymore not even you
this time you're wrong my are very
funny. You're going to commit another
murder. If you are going to murder me
you're saying no one was
not even you know right then please.
I love Joe and I were my love you
can destroy. That
there was. A little. I never had
I was. The only.
Just.
Not much time that I didn't bring you
that I had made plans to give up my act
of attending every available moment keeping
my right where it can relate I proved
them and then I learned
my rear end and your.
Right that they get. It we just have
a great. Ride.
I say what you mean by that. Private
joke. My retired people are
going to do when they do it. Right.
About lawyer got news for you.
Now I've got idea when I get married. Ride
a sailing party we're gonna get
there I want to live that.
Way I'm sorry. Or this was exactly. The.
Right. News in terms of the pain but
I've always wanted you know laughing
all the same you did mention
it or we said. I wanted to do.
The like to see we've been
with you but that meant.
I like your work I'd be willing
to pay that much twenty five and.
I'm not sure you know what about it
twenty five hundred. We don't we have.
Our hold on
a new one you know I
have. Belonged to you. I
am afraid where money is concerned
I'm going to be back. Looking.
For the best. When three and by
that my life in the two weeks
give it very well acquainted I'm looking
forward to it. Myron if you're one
weakness thinking men think.
Thank you but not when. They. Don't push
me. At all you can hear. I can
drop you one hundred thousand.
You take. I don't go to Paris No
I didn't try not for the money.
I need those two weeks needed time to
finish but I got it I promise you my RE
you're not going to have your job.
And you're not here I'm about. One who
believes in the honesty and integrity of our
court but that's something you would never
be able to understand what you're trying
to do you really understand what you did
to me when I learned you. You understand
and when even acquittal I begin to feel you
I want you to understand why I want you
to fully understand that we have to
pay for what we've done I don't take.
You. I did
better or worse.
Excellent than
a very patient. You know I have.
Great times you seem very.
Ervice. Try. To get
your. Action I think you have any worries.
If your party be just snap
or out either way. And.
Oh man of mystery I will not
press you. Stay on. The
right.
You just ordered another product.
And America you. You think
you're the only one.
Actor.
I can walk on the lead we could give them
a captain at Intel great attempting to come
out we can't do that and Greg has been
counting on it looking forward to it so
important. To talk about that effort in
America. Really was to go.
For dessert and I suggest Terry to Billy
it's actually. Thank you about human.
That was
a delicious dinner French food couldn't
be any better. Enjoy it then you told us
you tell us what it's all about after dinner.
Oh it's all right he just anxious you
may actually see the trip to
Paris and she's about to become
a bride. Back I want to know why.
Greg ordeal was four point five hundred I
thought I'd double it that's my surprise
. By helping me achieve
an important ambition.
Certainly hope through the
years. I'm certain it will
see. To me the park is
reflected not only French.
With understanding of self centered and
hope you never disappoint. I must run
and
a lot of work to do without. All that one
important case to mention that someone.
Thank you for coming. We'll see
you again probably yes you will.
Find
a way and it's something I've been wanting
to ask you. About the portrait of me it
turned out badly it suppose
you'd realize it made
a mistake in the manner
in which you. Do that.
Strike despite your face
spiralling strained
I always felt that the same
parallel existed in love.
Did not. Fight back.
It.
Can't tell you how good it is
nothing the matter with you Greg.
A something I want to ask. About Myra the.
Talk over. The jury to find Mary
guilty of first degree murder.
At the end of the trial the jury
found not guilty how did you find it
important to me I want
to know All right Greg
you're very convincing I understand
you're swearing that you're
a but you didn't sway me. But the time I
still thought she was guilty I was sure
you'd know about
a long time. Now I know that the the jury
brought in the correct verdict I've known
you too many years. You never would have
said it's just for the dramatic effect
another attorney might but you know I
admitted Monday Marilee in this case.
I was with space thank you very
well there's something I'd like you to do.
Thank you John.
With Iraq and you could make it to.
Getting laid I believe one of the
thanks of the talk of
a very help. The. It. Why
did you send for me are you talking to the
district attorney we were talking about
a case you OK this contest talk of you has
gone far enough you still think this is
a joke you've got to stop the
creek every time you took
a car the other evening at dinner I was
terrified what you're doing is until I
can't stand much more you're
a murderous mire anything that happens to
you won't be enough crazy the jury free
me they found me innocent all have want
to go away with cause she done this time
for the first time in my life I want to
be decently you don't know the meaning of
the word at first I thought like you but
it wasn't long before I changed my mind
food in my room just like you for me
to find to be heard by someone like you
I'm not going to let it happen no matter
what you tell him he won't leave you. No
way of proving I killed Joe this time
Frank Frey and. I never once meant
to threaten you I made you
a promise. I've compiled in
this fall there is no longer theory it's
proof the only way you can prevent me from
turning it over to. Is to kill
me. I'm not going to kill you
it must be maddening to know that in just
a little while you're going to lose
everything you planned and killed for you see
Myra you can't win any more.
We. Was not long before my
telephone began to ring I knew it would
be Myra she was that she wanted to see me
right away but I still had
a few things to do so I told her I'd
see her later at my office I made the
appointment for twelve
thirty sharp it was now only
a matter of waiting time to wait so now
the patterns complete and it's the
same pattern generally. But this time Myra
won't be acquitted that's where you are
concerned. Because this time you're not
going to have to guess whether or not
Myra's guilty you'll know going to be
a witness. RW
.
Thank you for being prompt
you promised me and.
I completely. Now Know attorney
to get you not even me. I can
say the same crime crime and I told you
I'm trying you before call folk will let
him determine whether or not
you're guilty would you prefer.
To kill and you can. Afford three of us
a. Call and I can come
right over to seeing
this if you still want to
marry him I read that. Don't.
Know maybe doing.
That to her crazies committed suicide.
What are you doing here he asked if I could
meet him here for twelve string told me
to be here twelve forty.
I'd never expect Craig to do
a thing like this. There's
really Willis. Man shot him self would
you send someone over right away please.
Chambers building room to. Know is that.
Tape recorder still running.
Could be Craig's way of
giving us an explanation.